[{"question": " wait. before we go in, i just want you to know i love you. i had a great time on our honeymoon, and i can&#146;t wait to go in there and spend the rest of our life together.", "answer": " you&#146;re really sticking with the shell necklace huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " hey! you&#146;re back!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " hi sweetie!", "answer": " come on in!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " so how was the honeymoon?", "answer": " oh, so much fun. but the best part is, we met this incredible couple on the way back.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " that was the best part?  good honeymooning tiger.", "answer": " no, they were really cool. they were on their honeymoon too!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " they&#146;re terrific, and they live right here in the city.", "answer": " yeah, can we go call them? is it too soon to call? i wanna call.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " i&#146;m sorry, we&#146;re just kinda excited because we finally have a couple to hang out with.", "answer": " i know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " a couple? like two people? like  one , two people?", "answer": " this is different! greg and jenny are in a relationship.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " oh, greg and jenny yuck!  hi greg, i&#146;m chandler this is monica. hi monica, this is jenny. hi jenny. hi greg.", "answer": " listen, they are really great. if you just got a chance&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " y&#146;know what? why don&#146;t you just give us our souvenirs and get the hell out of here?", "answer": " we really&#133;didn&#146;t get a chance to&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " you have got to be kidding me!", "answer": " we didn&#146;t get anything for anyone.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " hm-mm! yeah nice necklace!", "answer": " that you can have.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " hello!", "answer": " welcome home.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " so, how was the honeymoon?", "answer": " it was great! it was great! how about you?! i mean you&#146;re having a baby!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " oh! look! i have a sonogram picture!", "answer": " oh great!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " ross! it&#146;s got your wavy black lines!", "answer": " all right, so now that ross knows can you tell us y&#146;know how it happened? i mean, when did it happen? how many times did it happen?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " well it happened about six weeks ago, and uh i had just got home from work and ross was already there &#145;cause i guess he had been hanging out with joey.", "answer": " you&#146;re welcome buddy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " and so i had a lot of work to do so ross, nice guy that he is, offered to help me out. and then we had a little wine, we got to talking, and the next thing you know out of nowhere ross comes on to me.", "answer": "  umm that&#146;s&#133;that&#146;s a little misleading.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " what is?", "answer": " the lie you just told.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " that-that you came on to me?", "answer": " there&#146;s the one!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " but you did! i mean, let&#146;s be honest.", "answer": " yes let&#146;s. y&#146;know what? uh, it&#146;s-it&#146;s not important. what is important is that, is that we&#146;re having a baby. and it&#146;s not&#151;doesn&#146;t matter who came on to who.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " whom.  that&#146;s right.", "answer": " you know you kissed me first.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " what? what?! you were begging me to kiss you! you-you-you were sending me signals all over the place!", "answer": " i was sending you signals?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " yeah!", "answer": " oh please. okay, anyone in this room think that i would send ross begging symbols, please show of hands.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " y&#146;know what?! it doesn&#146;t matter! it doesn&#146;t matter what you believe! what matters is what happened!", "answer": " okay. so these signals ross, explain this to me, &#145;cause maybe i need to be more careful. i mean, am i sending you these signals right now?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " y&#146;know what? y&#146;know what? rachel, just-just drop it.", "answer": " no please, show me how i begged you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " i can&#146;t believe he taped the two of them having sex!", "answer": " yeah! you gotta tell a girl before you tape her. such a rookie mistake.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " y&#146;know who has a great video camera?", "answer": "  greg and jenny?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " do you still wanna call &#145;em? i wanna call &#145;em.", "answer": " let&#146;s call &#145;em.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": "  hello?  eighth street deli?", "answer": " hey, hang up! you get food poisoning just talkin&#146; to that place.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": "  hello?   it&#146;s the deli again!", "answer": " all right! i&#146;ll have a sandwich!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " you got fake numbered.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " what?! people don&#146;t do that!", "answer": " oh i think we do.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " they gave us a fake number? why? why would they do that?", "answer": " i don&#146;t know! you were a delight to talk to. you asked all those insightful, great questions.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " and you&#146;ve never been funnier. joke, joke, joke, you were a hoot!", "answer": " y&#146;know what? don&#146;t worry about it, you still got me and phoebe.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " excuse me, i don&#146;t want greg and jenny&#146;s rejects.", "answer": "  rachel won&#146;t talk to me! she won&#146;t even open the door!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " hmm, i wonder why. pervert!", "answer": " okay, listen i am not a pervert!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " that&#146;s like the pervert motto! yeah! yeah! they have you raise your right hand, put your left hand down your pants, and repeat that!", "answer": " filming rachel is not something i planned. okay look, here&#146;s what happened, and joey you-you can back me up on this. all right, about-about a month and a half ago i came to you with a problem? umm, a personal thing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " personal thing? what personal thing? i don&#146;t know.", "answer": " about&#133;about sex?  that i hadn&#146;t had sex in months?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " do you have a minute? i&#146;d like to talk to you about something i&#146;m, i&#146;m really uncomfortable talking about.", "answer": " sure. what? about uh, you showering with your mom?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " i actually had a topic in mind! i&#146;m, i&#146;m kinda going through a dry spell, sex wise.", "answer": " whoa, for like months?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " five to be lying, six.", "answer": " six months? whoa that&#146;s rough.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " well, i mean it&#146;s not all bad. i&#146;m learning to appreciate the uh, smaller things in life. like the sound of a bird and the color of the sky.", "answer": " the sky&#146;s blue ross and i had sex yesterday!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " please, help me! i have a date tonight. it has to go well okay&#151;i&#146;m scared for my health!", "answer": " okay. okay. umm&#133;ooh! oh-oh, i got something. it&#146;s this story i came up with, very romantic. i swear any woman that hears it; they&#146;re like putty.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " really? well then tell it to me.", "answer": " okay. now you&#146;re gonna want to have sex with me when you hear it, but you have to remember it is just the story.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": "  i&#146;ll try to control myself.", "answer": " okay.  years ago, when i was backpacking across western europe&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": "  you were backpacking across western europe?", "answer": " have a nice six more months ross!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": "  okay! okay! okay. i&#146;m sorry. please, please, you were in western europe and?", "answer": " i was just outside barcelona hiking in the foothills of mount tibidabo. i was at the end of this path and i came to a clearing and there was a lake, very secluded. and there were tall trees all around.  it was dead silent. gorgeous.  and across the lake i saw&#133;a beautiful woman&#133;bathing herself&#133;but she was crying&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " umm, this is great wine.", "answer": " it&#146;s from france&#133;in europe&#133;western europe. y&#146;know umm, a few years ago i actually was backpacking across western europe.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " really?", "answer": " uh-hmm&#151;wait! it gets better. um, yeah i was in barcelona.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " anyway, umm so i was um, i was hiking&#133;", "answer": " i love hiking!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": "  oh that&#146;s great! i was hiking along the foothills of mount tibidaybo&#133;", "answer": " i think its tibidabo.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " whoa! what are you doing here? how did your date go?", "answer": " great! i&#146;m across the street having sex with her right now. your story sucks!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " hey! look, if it didn&#146;t work it&#146;s because you didn&#146;t tell it right! show me how you did it.", "answer": " no! no, i don&#146;t&#133;don&#146;t want to.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " how long since you&#146;ve seen a girl naked?", "answer": " i was backpacking across western europe.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " i&#146;m not feeling it.", "answer": " i was just outside barcelona, hiking&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " no! no! no ross! i&#146;m not hot! are you hot?", "answer": " it&#146;s been six months! i&#146;m always hot!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " well you&#146;re not selling the story! it&#146;s like; it&#146;s like you don&#146;t believe it! look, i gotta go. i got a date, but try this. do what i do when i&#146;m preparing for an audition. okay? i&#146;ll set you up with my video camera and you can record yourself and-and see what you&#146;re doing wrong.", "answer": " i&#146;ll try that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " all right now&#133; all right, you&#146;re all set up. you&#146;re good to go. just hit record. all right?", "answer": " thanks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " good luck.", "answer": " thanks. and-and hey joe?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " yeah?", "answer": " listen, if you ever have any problem with the ladies you know i&#146;ll help you out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " hello! can i get you anything? huh? lens cleaner? your battery okay?  rachel!", "answer": " oh ross!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " thank god you&#146;re here! you have to help me! were you just talking to yourself?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " yeah, definitely.", "answer": " what a great idea! that will get rachel to forgive me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " y&#146;know what? this is not fair to her. let&#146;s just forget the tape!", "answer": " thank you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " joey! no!", "answer": " loud and clear!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " i still don't get why greg and jenny would give us a fake number.", "answer": " y&#146;know, if they knew what they were doing they probably didn&#146;t give you real names either.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " okay, maybe people give out fake numbers, but they don&#146;t give out fake names.", "answer": " oh yeah?  hi, ken adams, nice to meet you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " i still don&#146;t get it, we didn&#146;t do anything wrong.", "answer": " i know! although, you did tell an awful lot of jokes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " i thought you said those jokes were funny. joke! joke! joke!", "answer": "  joke. joke. blah! blah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " well maybe it was all of your questions.", "answer": " what about my questions?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " the sheer volume, it was like flying with the riddler!", "answer": " oh, i&#146;m sorry. was that another joke?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": "  was that another question?", "answer": "  hey! is ross still here?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " uh no rach, he&#146;s gone. but listen, he told us what happened and it does, it sounds like an honest mistake.", "answer": " oh really? well how would you like it if i had sex with you and i taped it?  oh forget it!  oh there he is now, the father of my child, the porn king of the west village.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " thank you.  what?  you don&#146;t want to see this do you?", "answer": " hell yeah!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " i am not gonna show you this!", "answer": " no! not the sex part, just the stuff leading up to it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " forget it, she&#146;s destroying it.", "answer": " okay fine! fine! we&#146;ll just have to think of some other way to put the whole &#145;who came onto who,&#146; thing to rest! come on now, think!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " look, forget it phoebe. okay? it&#146;s rachel&#146;s tape and she can do whatever she wants with it. and she wants to destroy it. so, end of story.", "answer": " i wanna see it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " clearly you don&#146;t want people to see this tape. now i don&#146;t want people to see this tape either, but you so badly don&#146;t people to see it makes me want to see it. you see?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": "  are we watchin&#146; the tape or not?!", "answer": " i don&#146;t want people to see it for your sake.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " rachel, please&#133;", "answer": " ah, a little preview!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": "  hello! can i get you anything?", "answer": "  i&#146;m so happy! commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": "  oh, thank god you&#146;re here! you have to help me! were you just talking to yourself?", "answer": " there i am.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " you&#146;re gonna get pregnant.", "answer": "  i screwed up so bad, i told monica that i would stuff and send all these wedding invitations like weeks ago and i-i&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": "  you didn&#146;t do it?", "answer": "  i-i know&#151;i had put them in&#133;in-in my desk at work and i completely forgot about them until today.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": "  sweetie okay. it&#146;s okay. everybody made it to the wedding. i&#146;m fine.", "answer": " kinda hurtin&#146; my hand though.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " i know.", "answer": "   i cannot believe that i did this. especially after monica just went on and on and on about it!  &quot;okay rachel! here are the invitations rachel! now be very careful rachel! please, drinking no liquids around the invitations rachel!&quot;  whoa oh! oh-oh-oh! oh&#133;oh-oh-oh&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " did you do it on our invitations?!", "answer": "  not on the ones we sent out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": "  can you believe this is already happening? i mean it seems like yesterday they just got engaged.", "answer": "  i know. hey remember&#133;remember the night they got engaged? how uh, you and i almost&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": "  oh, i remember how we almost. do you think we would&#146;ve gone through with it? y&#146;know, if we hadn&#146;t gotten caught. do you think we would&#146;ve done it?", "answer": "  i mean i&#133;i know i wanted to. i just, i just wasn&#146;t sure if you wanted to.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": "  so we&#133;we both wanted to.", "answer": "  interesting.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": "  yeah.  anyway umm, it probably worked out for the best.", "answer": "  oh yeah, sure.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " okay, in about ten seconds you&#146;re gonna see him kiss me.", "answer": " and in about five seconds you&#146;re gonna see why.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " okay, get ready to see some beggin&#146;!", "answer": " oh, you came on to ross!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " now i&#146;m so happy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " what are you talking about?!", "answer": " you used the europe story!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " that&#146;s the magic story you use when you wanna have sex!", "answer": " how do you know about that story?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " how do you know about that story?!", "answer": " i heard it from my friend irene who heard it from some guy!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " no. no, she told me his name was ken adams.", "answer": "  ken adams!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " hi.", "answer": " so uh, apparently people are familiar with the europe story?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " yeah. listen about that, the whole uh, who came on to who thing really doesn&#146;t matter. i mean, i think it would&#146;ve happened either way. i mean if you hadn&#146;t initiated it i-i-i know i would&#146;ve.", "answer": " it was an amazing night.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " you think it looked amazing?", "answer": " i uh&#133; i don&#146;t know. i mean i&#133;i honestly didn&#146;t watch", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " yeah, me neither. yet&#133;", "answer": " uhhhhhh&#133;that-that may be weird.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " good luck.", "answer": " good luck to you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " mind if i mute?", "answer": " oh please.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " oh, oh there go the clothes.", "answer": " you are undressing very quickly.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " six months rachel, six months. ross and rachel: ah.  oh.", "answer": " hey. we-we look&#133;we look pretty good.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " that&#146;s what i was gonna say.", "answer": " oh nice tan!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " thank you! i had just gone to the beach that weekend.", "answer": " ah&#133;.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " have you been working out?", "answer": " i have been working out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " really? wow, this is so much better than i&#133; ross and rachel: ohh! ew!", "answer": " oh that&#146;s not pretty.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": " oh! oh!", "answer": " no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": " oh god!", "answer": " oh no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 285, "asentId": 286}, {"question": " oh, make it stop!", "answer": " oh no!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 287, "asentId": 288}, {"question": " make it stop!!", "answer": " no!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 289, "asentId": 290}, {"question": " have to make it stop!!", "answer": " no!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 291, "asentId": 292}, {"question": "  hello greg?  hi, this is monica from the plane? listen, the number that you gave me 853-5&#133;   that is their old number! jenny&#146;s been giving it out since they moved!", "answer": " jenny! that is so jenny!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 293, "asentId": 294}]